MY WORK

Showreel: https://youtu.be/oYNCpvGWHsk

MY EXPERTISE

Cloth Simulation
Garment Modelling
3D Animation
3D Modelling
Rendering
Visual Effects
Graphic Design
Problem Solving
Communication
Time Management

SOFTWARE KNOWLEDGE Illustrator - 8+ Years Photoshop - 3+ Years Premiere Pro - 3+ Years Adobe XD - 2 Years After Effects - 1 Year Animate - 1 Year InDesign - 1 Year Dreamweaver - 1 Year Maya - 3+ Years Arnold - 3+ Years 3DS Max - < 1 Year Unity - 2 Years Houdini - < 1 Years Marvelous

Designer - < 1 Year

DESRAY SPENCER

GRADUATE 3D GENERALIST

Desrayspencer@gmail.com

Website:

https://desrayspencer.wixsite.com/desray-designs

I am a highly industrious and creative young person who is pursuing a career within the 3D Computer Graphics industry. I have a strong interest in 3D Animation, 3D Modelling, and Visual Effects. I am a person who values knowledge and I am always happy to learn new skills and further develop my existing skills. I have strong communication, customer service, and team working skills gained from my marketing and hospitality experiences.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 - 2023 BARTENDER

Catford Constitunal | Currently Employed

SUPERVISOR

Ninth Life | Part time

SUPERVISOR

Ladywell Tavern | Part time

2018 - 2022 BARTENDER

Various Companies | Part time during studies

Further developed my communication, teamworking, customer service, and bartending skills.

2016 STUDIO ASSISTANT

Inky CuttleFish | Traineeship

- Developed traditional printmaking techniques and skills for lino printing, screen printing, etching, and letterpress
- Assisted with managing social media accounts and e-mail marketing using Mail Chimp
- Created posters for events happening at the studio
- Participated in the 20:20 Print Exchange Exhibition

2016 MARKETING ASSISTANT

New Peak | Part time

 Developed F2F skills, team working, customer service, and communication skills

DESRAY SPENCER

GRADUATE 3D GENERALIST

Desrayspencer@gmail.com

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

HTML / CSS - 2 Years

JavaScript / P5.js - 2 Years

C# - 2 Years

HOBBIES

Gaming
Computer Graphics
Record Collecting

CONNECT WITH ME ON

LinkedIn: Desray Spencer

REFERENCES

Martyn Broadhead - University Lecturer

EDUCATION HISTORY

2019 - 2022 BSC H DIGITAL MEDIA DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT

University of Greenwich | First Class Honours

Focused on 3D Animation and Modelling including advanced techniques. Other modules taken include; game development, programming for web and games, digital media design and campaign marketing, cinematics and visual storytelling, sound design, and motion graphics. My final year project focused on rigging a non-biped character and replicating wing motion using cloth simulation.

2017 - 2019 BTEC LEVEL 3 ART & DESIGN

Southwark College | MMP

2017 DIPLOMA IN GRAPHIC DESIGN

Shaw Academy | Merit

2017 DIPLOMA IN MOBILE APP DEVELOPMENT

Shaw Academy | Merit

2016 OCR FUNCTIONAL SKILLS IN MATHS

Big Creative Education | Pass

2012 - 2016 5 GCSE GRADE B - C INCLUDING ENGLISH

Trinity C of E Secondary School

CERTIFICATES

2016 NOCN LEVEL 2 AWARD IN EMPLOYABILITY

Big Creative Education